<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oscuro Quintet</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oscuro Quintet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinjoo Cho</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/shinjoo-cho/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/shinjoo-cho/</guid>
      <description>Bandoneonist, pianist, and accordionist Shinjoo began her piano study in Korea at the age of five and in the US, she studied with Peter Coraggio and Ingrid Clarfield and attended Westminster Choir College in Princeton, NJ. Her path to the music of other cultures began with studies in Serbia and Argentina. Shinjoo has collaborated with international music, dance, and film artists in multi-disciplinary projects as an improviser and an ensemble musician, with performances in the US, Canada, Korea, and Argentina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joseph Kauffman</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/joseph-kauffman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/joseph-kauffman/</guid>
      <description>Joseph began his violin studies at the age of five and studied with Yayoi Numazawa, James Lyon, Max Zorin, and Eduard Schmieder. He holds violin performance degrees from Pennsylvania State University (BM) and Temple University (MM) with distinction. As violinist and violist, Joseph has appeared as a soloist with Temple Symphony Orchestra, Williamsport Chamber Orchestra, and Pennsylvania State University Philharmonic and has performed on prestigious concert stages in the US, France, Austria, Chile, Germany, and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Boyadjian</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/antonio-boyadjian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/antonio-boyadjian/</guid>
      <description>Antonio is a Latin Grammy nominated pianist, composer, producer, and sound engineer. Native of Argentina, he began his music studies with piano and guitar and attended National Conservatory of Buenos Aires and National University of the Arts.
He studied tango and jazz with Dino Saluzzi, Manuel Fraga, Anibal Gluzman, and Hernan Possetti. Antonio writes and produces original music for film, theater, and commercials. In 2006 he joined an electrotango group Tanghetto and released seven albums and received two Gardel Awards and a Latin Grammy nomination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Klinke</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/jason-klinke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/jason-klinke/</guid>
      <description>Guitarist and piano technician Jason began studying the guitar at age 11 and attended Temple University’s Esther Boyer College of Music. He studied under the likes of Tom Giacobetti, Terrell Stafford, Bruce Barth, and Joseph Federico. He has worked with many of the area’s top jazz musicians including Larry McKenna, Byron Landham, Akiko Tsuruga, and Mike Boone and has performed at the Philadelphia Museum of Art, Barnes Museum, Keswick Theater, Center City Jazz Fest, Bethlehem Music Fest, Somers Point Jazz Fest, and Jazz Bridge Concerts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Blazer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/ben-blazer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/ben-blazer/</guid>
      <description>Benjamin Blazer attended Temple University, where he attained a BM in music theory and double bass performance, as well as an MM in music composition. He studied double bass with John Hood of the Philadelphia Orchestra and composition with Matthew Greenbaum, Maurice Wright and Richard Brodhead.
Benjamin currently thrives in the field of music education as the music department chair for Central High School in the School District of Philadelphia as well as an adjunct faculty member for the Music Preparatory Division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Coyle</title>
      <link>http://example.org/performers/chris-coyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/performers/chris-coyle/</guid>
      <description>Chris is a bassist, composer and music educator based in Philadelphia. As a very active performer, he can be found in an array of musical settings with: his own Outside Sound jazz ensemble and noted jazz musicians such as John Swana, Behn Gillece, and V. Shayne Frederick; Americana music with Noggin Hill and Lady Bird; experimental music with Son Step and Rhinoceri Trio; and world Music with Conjunto Philadelphia and Ensemble Novo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Event</title>
      <link>http://example.org/events/07-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/events/07-25/</guid>
      <description>FOSSCON brings together users of Free and Open Source Software from a wide variety of fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Event</title>
      <link>http://example.org/events/08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/events/08-25/</guid>
      <description>FOSSCON brings together users of Free and Open Source Software from a wide variety of fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Event</title>
      <link>http://example.org/events/09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/events/09-10/</guid>
      <description>SaltConf18 is a gathering designed to help systems administrators, cloud architects, enterprise IT operators, site reliability engineers, IT directors, and IT managers more effectively manage and secure data center infrastructure using SaltStack event-driven automation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>